Why am I here now?
[Shindecent]
[Is shooting going well?]
[Please call me]
I could just text him
[Don't bail me
and let's talk]
[Shindecent]
Take it
Seems like
an important call
Thank you
for the coffee truck
I'm here to say this
Did the shooting
go well?
I ruined it
Don't worry
You've always
done great…
Are you gonna say
I don't know about you?
I'm sorry about
what happened that day
That's surprising
I didn't expect
your apology
Physical affections
like that…
Dating and breaking up…
Isn't that nothing
for someone like you?
Or…
are you sorry
for toying
with my feelings?
Did I make you confused?
I'm saying sorry for
showing my feelings
not for toying
with yours
Do you…
like me?